In this neighborhood, the streets are filled with senior citizens.
Rudeon County is a coastal region with the most rapidly aging population in China.
China began its national one-child policy in 1978 to control the ballooning population.
Rudong is known as the birthplace of the policy, having launched their 10 years earlier.
But now, the shrinking population of working adults and increasing cost of social security
are hampering economic growth in China.
Six years ago, the Chinese government abolished
the one child policy and allowed couples to give birth
to a second child.
In August 2021, it permitted a third child.
The big city is still in the same state.
So I think it's not that you're born.
It will take care of your teeth,
and the words will be said.
Really?
Don't worry.
Over the years, people's values and concerns have changed.
From the birthplace of the one child policy,
we look at the current state of China's grain population.
Ruedong is 100 kilometers north of Shanghai.
It's a coastal county located in Jiangsu Province.
About 36% of Rudom's population of around 900,000 is aged 65 or older, the highest ratio of elderly in China.
Some residents of Rudom are even centenarians.
Every month, local volunteers and doctors offer free health checks.
has 35 nursing homes.
The Baihua nursing home is a large-scale facility
that accommodates 100 residents.
It was built by the local government and is run privately.
This partnership between the public and private sector
manages to keep costs lower than other facilities.
In China, the five welfare costs describe housing, food, clothing, health care, and funeral costs.
Many of the residents at the nursing home have no family, no income, and no ability to work.
On a national level, the percentage of seniors over 65 within the population has increased
by 60% from 2010 to 2020.
Social welfare costs have tripled in the past 10 years.
This year, expenses reached $800 billion US dollars,
four times the national defense costs.
When the People's Republic of China was founded in 1949,
Its population was 540 million, less than half of what it is now.
Initially, Communist Party Chairman Mao Zeteng urged the Chinese to have many children,
feeling that a large labor force was necessary to strengthen the country.
85-year-old Xu Zhun is a resident at the Baihou Nursing Home.
He raised five children almost 15 years before the one-child policy began.
In the next three decades, the population exploded by 400 million.
The skyrocketing population caused shortages in food and housing, increased unemployment,
and other major social problems.
Then I said, I don't want to know what I want.
That I wanted to know is that I am a big source of responsibility.
I don't give up.
I have to fill it up.
I needed to have enough money.
I started talking about this when I had a new job.
The Chinese government began the one child policy.
In 1978, when it also started its economic reform and open-door policy, population control
slogans were written all over town.
After the first birth, contraceptive rings, after the second birth, sterilization.
For the third birth, abortion and confiscation of assets.
In Ruedong, local residents were chosen as officials to enforce the one child policy.
We were in a rush.
We had to take a rest.
Jingzhou Xiang was just 17 years old when she was appointed as a public official
to watch over the reproductive states of more than 1,000 women.
ừa
e
As a public official, Jin's job was to seek out women who had concealed their pregnancies
and pressure them into getting abortions.
We don't have to go to the hospital, but we have to go to the hospital.
We don't have to go to the hospital.
They have to fight with us, and our brain.
This is a way to get rid of them.
What is the most expensive thing?
The customer can't understand.
What is the most important thing to do?
It's just to get the job done.
In just ten years since the one-child policy was implemented in Rudeung,
its reported that 99 percent of child-bearing age women gave birth to no more than one
child due to sterilization.
In words, Rudeung was widely publicized over radio and TV as being the most successful
region for the policy.
This is a nursing care facility for the elderly in a suburban area of the county.
Jin, who enforced the one child policy for almost 30 years, currently works here.
Many residents need constant assistance to eat or use the bathroom due to physical challenges.
Jin's husband, Chen Jinguo, is also a resident here.
Jin contracted prostate cancer two years ago, received surgery and became physically disabled as a result.
Neither Jane nor her husband, who worked as a fisherman at a rural farming village, are eligible for pension, since they're registered as farmers on their family record.
She's 300 yuan.
Yeah, she's 300 yuan.
We can eat two more.
Two more.
Eat more.
Neither Jing nor her husband,
who worked as a fisherman at a rural farming village,
are eligible for pension
since they're registered as farmers on their family record.
Jing gave birth to a son at the age of 26,
but her son now lives in the city
and Jing says she can't rely on him.
The elderly residents here are living solitary lives.
According to government research, the one child policy prevented the births of 400 million
children.
China's working population has diminished by 4% since peaking in 2013.
This means the number of working adults supporting each senior citizen continues to decline.
In October of 2015, the Chinese government announced that it would end the one-child policy
that had been in place for more than 35 years.
This meant that all couples were finally allowed to give birth to a second child.
But six years later, China's birth rate continues to decrease rather than increase.
Xu Zhu Feng works as a doctor at the same facility as Zheng.
Xu had a daughter under the one child policy.
She hopes that her daughter will have a second child.
Today, she's visiting her daughter's family for the first time in four months.
Her daughter, Zhao Xiaoli, lives around an hour's drive south of Rudong.
The home is in a wealthy residential area in the suburbs of Shanghai.
The family purchased a luxurious three-story home four years ago.
Zhao lives here with her husband and son.
Her husband, Ho Zhao, runs a chemical materials company.
This is the best food we can eat.
I can go now.
Zhao is a stay-at-home mother.
Her son attends an international school,
where the yearly tuition is $18,000.
She hopes he'll be able to study abroad in the future.
According to a 2019 study,
education costs through junior high graduation
average $80,000 per child in Shanghai.
China's steadily rising cost of education
has made parents reluctant to have more children.
Since the birth of their son,
the family has repeatedly discussed
whether to have another child.
He was so small.
The sun is too dark.
You are not in the mountains.
You are in Shanghai.
I had a meeting with some of the young men at home,
and I had one of them come back to pick up the house and go there.
I thought it was a different place for the future.
How did you get your child?
This is quite a big deal.
If she had the right to see the situation
I wouldn't have been able to get any good things from her.
It's a big deal.
She says she now questions the one child policy, which she so readily accepted in the past.
They can't make it.
Don't do that.
It's a pure dream.
What?
I'm a dreamer.
When I said this,
I said,
now there are two different languages in the family.
There are many languages in the country.
I think that many people have seen me for a long time.
My mom said that she taught me about a thousand times a month.
And I don't care.
I want to eat a fruit that no one can eat.
So I think it's not that you're born.
She will take care of you.
What kind of teeth are these?
Really.
Don't forget.
Like us,
you think we're born in our second child.
And then you forget that we're not able to take care of her.
You mean, I don't think it's that bad.
I think now when you get to the hospital,
you don't really have to go to the hospital.
Do you think it's that bad?
Where do you think you're from?
You know, the hospital.
When I came to Shanghai, I had to stay with my friends.
I was going to a kids' home with them.
or the Dragon Boat Festival.
It's a celebratory day on which families often gather.
But Jing has no plans to see her own son.
How long have you been seeing her?
About a year.
About a year?
Is it a year?
A year.
There are still children and children.
And the children.
This is the birth of the children.
The birth of the children.
Take them to the children.
Take them to my son.
You can go there together.
I'm sorry, but I'm not.
I'm not able to open it.
We traveled two hours on Jing's behalf to Wu Shi in Jiangsu Province.
Hello, hello, hello.
Thank you, mom.
No need.
Just a little.
This man is Jing's son, Chen Feng.
I've never seen you before.
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
Why don't you go back to the house and see his past?
The whole street is full of money.
Full of money.
Yes.
Jin lives with his wife and daughter.
He bought his home for $280,000 three years ago
after borrowing money from the bank and his relatives.
He recalls that four years ago, they considered having a second child.
Two of them are selling the goods.
You can buy the parents.
Four or five years.
That's the parents' good news.
After graduating from junior high school,
Chen joined the military.
He now works at a military factory.
His wife works part-time.
Together, they make about $1,800 a month.
Their daughter is a military officer.
She is a military officer.
$1 a month.
Their daughter is turning 14 this year.
She's busy studying for next year's high school entrance
exams, under stress from his parents' health, the mortgage,
and his daughter's tuition.
She and decided to give up on having a second child.
I have been planning to sell to you for a year.
I have been working for the world for every word and every 4,000 years.
I have been working for the world for a year and every 1.5 years for my family.
I'm sorry.
We can afford to pay for our own money.
It's about one month.
Two thousand yuan.
I've sent a video.
Come here.
You're a good girl.
You're so stupid.
Chen's generation, who were born when the one child policy began, are now in their mid-40s.
It's an age when numerous stress factors collide, such as aging parents or rising education
costs for children.
The one child policy began as a way to escape poverty caused as a side effect of the booming population.
The Chinese government announced in August of 2021 that would allow couples to give birth
to up to three children.
As to whether the new effort will be enough to encourage births and slow the rapidly aging
population, only time will tell.